Burns, Eveline M. Collection of Publications 5441
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- British Labour. General [folder 1 of 2], 1922-1929 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Item 1: What Is the Red International of Labour Unions, 1927; Publication (Box 1, Folder 31)
    Author: A. Lozovsky
  - Item 2: Towards One Building Workers' Union: A Constitution, Publication (Box 1, Folder 31)
    Author: Building Workers' Minority Movement
  - Item 3: Workers' Control in the Distributive Industry: A Plan for Co-Operative Employees and Shop Workers, Publication (Box 1, Folder 31)
    Author: G. D. H. Cole
    Notes: Workers' Control Series, no.2. Reprinted form Chaos and Order in Industry
  - Item 4: Constitution and Rules, 1929; Publication (Box 1, Folder 31)
    Author: Fred Thompson; Frank Rowland
  - Item 5: The British Labour Movement: A Historical Introduction for Classes and Study Circles, 1922; Publication (Box 1, Folder 31)
    Notes: Syllabus Series, no.1. Third Edition
  - Item 6: Adam Smith: An Address, 1924; Publication (Box 1, Folder 31)
    Author: J. Bonar
    Notes: January 30, 1924. Political and Economic Circle, Transactions: Part 99.
  - Item 7: The Crisis: What It Is, How It Arose, What To Do, Publication (Box 1, Folder 31)
    Author: Ernest Bevin; G. D. H. Cole
  - Item 8: What is Wrong with the British Iron and Steel Industry? A Statement of Policy Involving Private Enterprise, the Workers, and the Nation, 1931; Publication (Box 1, Folder 31)
    Author: The Iron and Steel Trades Confederation
- British Labour. General [folder 2 of 2], 1896-1935 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Item 1: A Contribution to the Study of a Constant Standard and Just Measure of Value, 1896; Publication (Box 1, Folder 32)
    Author: T. N. Whitelaw
  - Item 2: The House of Industry: A New Estate of the Realm, 1931; Publication (Box 1, Folder 32)
    Author: S. G. Hobson; A. M. Wall; A. A. Purcell
  - Item 3: The Entrance to Industry, 1935; Publication (Box 1, Folder 32)
    Author: PEP (Political and Economic Planning)
    Notes: May 1935.
- The Labour Woman: A Political Monthly Journal for Working Women, 1930-1932 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: The Labour Woman: A Political Monthly Journal for Working Women, 1930; Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Author: Marion Phillips
    Notes: v.18:no.6 (1930:June)
  - Item 2: The Labour Woman: A Political Monthly Journal for Working Women, 1930; Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.18:no.7 (1930:July)
  - Item 3: The Labour Woman: A Political Monthly Journal for Working Women, 1930; Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.18:no.8 (1930:Aug.)
  - Item 4: The Labour Woman: A Political Monthly Journal for Working Women, 1930; Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.18:no.9 (1930:Sept.)
  - Item 5: The Labour Woman: A Political Monthly Journal for Working Women, 1930; Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.18:no.10 (1930:Oct.)
  - Item 6: The Labour Woman: A Political Monthly Journal for Working Women, 1930; Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.18:no.11 (1930:Nov.)
  - Item 7: The Labour Woman: A Political Monthly Journal for Working Women, 1930; Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.18:no.12 (1930:Dec.)
  - Item 8: The Labour Woman: A Political Monthly Journal for Working Women, 1931; Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.19:no.1 (1931:Jan.)
  - Item 9: The Labour Woman: A Political Monthly Journal for Working Women, 1931; Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.19:no.2 (1931:Feb.)
  - Item 10: The Labour Woman: A Political Monthly Journal for Working Women, 1931; Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.19:no.3 (1931:Mar.)
  - Item 11: The Labour Woman: A Political Monthly Journal for Working Women, 1931; Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.19:no.4 (1931:Apr.)
  - Item 12: The Labour Woman: A Political Monthly Journal for Working Women, 1931; Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.19:no.5 (1931:May)
  - Item 13: The Labour Woman: A Political Monthly Journal for Working Women, 1931; Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.19:no.7 (1931:July)
  - Item 14: The Labour Woman: A Political Monthly Journal for Working Women, 1932; Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Author: Mrs. Ayrton Gould
    Notes: v.20:no.5 (1932:May)
  - Item 15: The Labour Woman: A Political Monthly Journal for Working Women, 1932; Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.20:no.6 (1932:June)
  - Item 16: The Labour Woman: A Political Monthly Journal for Working Women, 1932; Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.20:no.7 (1932:July)
  - Item 17: The Labour Woman: A Political Monthly Journal for Working Women, 1932; Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Author: Mary E. Sutherland
    Notes: v.20:no.8 (1932:Aug.)
  - Item 18: The Labour Woman: A Political Monthly Journal for Working Women, 1932; Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.20:no.9 (1932:Sept.)
  - Item 19: The Labour Woman: A Political Monthly Journal for Working Women, 1932; Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.20:no.10 (1932:Oct.)
  - Item 20: The Labour Woman: A Political Monthly Journal for Working Women, 1932; Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.20:no.12 (1932:Dec.)
- The Labour Woman: A Political Monthly Journal for Working Women, 1933-1935 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: The Labour Woman: A Political Monthly Journal for Working Women, 1933; Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.21:no.1 (1933:Jan.)
  - Item 2: The Labour Woman: A Political Monthly Journal for Working Women, 1933; Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.21:no.2 (1933:Feb.)
  - Item 3: The Labour Woman: A Political Monthly Journal for Working Women, 1933; Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.21:no.3 (1933:Mar.)
  - Item 4: The Labour Woman: A Political Monthly Journal for Working Women, 1933; Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.21:no.4 (1933:Apr.)
  - Item 5: The Labour Woman: A Political Monthly Journal for Working Women, 1933; Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.21:no.5 (1933:May)
  - Item 6: The Labour Woman: A Political Monthly Journal for Working Women, 1933; Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.21:no.6 (1933:June)
  - Item 7: The Labour Woman: A Political Monthly Journal for Working Women, 1933; Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.21:no.7 (1933:July)
  - Item 8: The Labour Woman: A Political Monthly Journal for Working Women, 1933; Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.21:no.8 (1933:Aug.)
  - Item 9: The Labour Woman: A Political Monthly Journal for Working Women, 1933; Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.21:no.9 (1933:Sept.)
  - Item 10: The Labour Woman: A Political Monthly Journal for Working Women, 1933; Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.21:no.10 (1933:Oct.)
  - Item 11: The Labour Woman: A Political Monthly Journal for Working Women, 1933; Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.21:no.11 (1933:Nov)
  - Item 12: The Labour Woman: A Political Monthly Journal for Working Women, 1933; Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.21:no.12 (1933:Dec.)
  - Item 13: The Labour Woman: A Political Monthly Journal for Working Women, 1934; Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.22:no.1 (1934:Jan.)
  - Item 14: The Labour Woman: A Political Monthly Journal for Working Women, 1934; Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.22:no.2 (1934:Feb.)
  - Item 15: The Labour Woman: A Political Monthly Journal for Working Women, 1934; Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.22:no.3 (1934:Mar.)
  - Item 16: The Labour Woman: A Political Monthly Journal for Working Women, 1934; Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.22:no.4 (1934:Apr.)
  - Item 17: The Labour Woman: A Political Monthly Journal for Working Women, 1934; Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.22:no.5 (1934:May)
  - Item 18: The Labour Woman: A Political Monthly Journal for Working Women, 1934; Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.22:no.6 (1934:June)
  - Item 19: The Labour Woman: A Political Monthly Journal for Working Women, 1934; Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.22:no.7 (1934:July)
  - Item 20: The Labour Woman: A Political Monthly Journal for Working Women, 1934; Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.22:no.8 (1934:Aug.)
  - Item 21: The Labour Woman: A Political Monthly Journal for Working Women, 1934; Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.22:no.9 (1934:Sept.)
  - Item 22: The Labour Woman: A Political Monthly Journal for Working Women, 1934; Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.22:no.10 (1934:Oct.)
  - Item 23: The Labour Woman: A Political Monthly Journal for Working Women, 1934; Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.22:no.11 (1934:Nov)
  - Item 24: The Labour Woman: A Political Monthly Journal for Working Women, 1934; Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.22:no.12 (1934:Dec.)
  - Item 25: The Labour Woman: A Political Monthly Journal for Working Women, 1935; Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.23:no.1 (1935:Jan.)
  - Item 26: The Labour Woman: A Political Monthly Journal for Working Women, 1935; Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.23:no.2 (1935:Feb.)
  - Item 27: The Labour Woman: A Political Monthly Journal for Working Women, 1935; Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.23:no.3 (1935:Mar.)
  - Item 28: The Labour Woman: A Political Monthly Journal for Working Women, 1935; Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.23:no.5 (1935:May)
  - Item 29: The Labour Woman: A Political Monthly Journal for Working Women, 1935; Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.23:no.6 (1935:June)
- Local Government Department., 1937; Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Outdoor Relief Scales, 1937; Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Author: Local Government Department
    Notes: August, 1937. L.G.34
- Industrial News: For the Use of the Press, 1936-1937 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Industrial News: For the Use of the Press, 1936; Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
    Author: Publicity Department
    Notes: no.485 (1936:May 19)
  - Item 2: Industrial News: For the Use of the Press, 1936; Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
    Notes: no.487 (1936:June 16)
  - Item 3: Industrial News: For the Use of the Press, 1936; Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
    Notes: no.489 (1936:July 14)
  - Item 4: Industrial News: For the Use of the Press, 1936; Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
    Notes: no.490 (1936:July 28)
  - Item 5: Industrial News: For the Use of the Press, 1936; Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
    Notes: no.491 (1936:Aug. 4)
  - Item 6: Industrial News: For the Use of the Press, 1936; Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
    Notes: no.492 (1936:Aug. 18)
  - Item 7: Industrial News: For the Use of the Press, 1936; Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
    Notes: no.495 (1936:Sept. 15)
  - Item 8: Industrial News: For the Use of the Press, 1936; Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
    Notes: no.496 (1936:Sept. 29)
  - Item 9: Industrial News: For the Use of the Press, 1936; Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
    Notes: no.497 (1936:Oct. 13)
  - Item 10: Industrial News: For the Use of the Press, 1936; Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
    Notes: no.498 (1936:Oct. 27)
  - Item 11: Industrial News: For the Use of the Press, 1936; Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
    Notes: no.499 (1936:Nov. 10)
  - Item 12: Industrial News: For the Use of the Press, 1936; Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
    Notes: no.500 (1936:Nov. 24)
  - Item 13: Industrial News: For the Use of the Press, 1936; Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
    Notes: no.502 (1936:Dec. 22)
  - Item 14: Industrial News: For the Use of the Press, 1937; Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
    Notes: no.502 (1937:Jan. 5)
  - Item 15: Industrial News: For the Use of the Press, 1937; Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
    Notes: no.506 (1937:Feb. 16)
  - Item 16: Industrial News: For the Use of the Press, 1937; Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
    Notes: no.508 (1937:Mar. 16)
  - Item 17: Industrial News: For the Use of the Press, 1937; Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
    Notes: no.511 (1937:May 4)
  - Item 18: Industrial News: For the Use of the Press, 1937; Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
    Notes: no.519 (1937:Aug. 31)
- The Labour Party. Labour: A Magazine for All Workers, 1933-1934 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Labour: A Magazine for All Workers, 1933; Publication (Box 2, Folder 5)
    Author: TUC (Trades Union Congress); The Labour Party
    Notes: v.1:no.1 (1933:Sept.)
  - Item 2: Labour: A Magazine for All Workers, 1933; Publication (Box 2, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.1:no.2 (1933:Oct.)
  - Item 3: Labour: A Magazine for All Workers, 1933; Publication (Box 2, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.1:no.3 (1933:Nov.)
  - Item 4: Labour: A Magazine for All Workers, 1933; Publication (Box 2, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.1:no.4 (1933:Dec.)
  - Item 5: Labour: A Magazine for All Workers, 1934; Publication (Box 2, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.1:no.5 (1934:Jan.)
  - Item 6: Labour: A Magazine for All Workers, 1934; Publication (Box 2, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.1:no.6 (1934:Feb.)
  - Item 7: Labour: A Magazine for All Workers, 1934; Publication (Box 2, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.1:no.7 (1934:Mar.)
  - Item 8: Labour: A Magazine for All Workers, 1934; Publication (Box 2, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.1:no.8 (1934:Apr.)
  - Item 9: Labour: A Magazine for All Workers, 1934; Publication (Box 2, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.1:no.9 (1934:May)
  - Item 10: Labour: A Magazine for All Workers, 1934; Publication (Box 2, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.1:no.10 (1934:June)
  - Item 11: Labour: A Magazine for All Workers, 1934; Publication (Box 2, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.1:no.11 (1934:July)
  - Item 12: Labour: A Magazine for All Workers, 1934; Publication (Box 2, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.1:no.12 (1934:Aug.)
  - Item 13: Labour: A Magazine for All Workers. Index, 1933-1934 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.1, September 1933 - August 1934
- The Labour Party. Labour: A Magazine for All Workers, 1934-1935 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Labour: A Magazine for All Workers, 1934; Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.2:no.1 (1933:Sept.)
  - Item 2: Labour: A Magazine for All Workers, 1934; Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.2:no.2 (1933:Oct.)
  - Item 3: Labour: A Magazine for All Workers, 1934; Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.2:no.3 (1933:Nov.)
  - Item 4: Labour: A Magazine for All Workers, 1934; Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.2:no.4 (1933:Dec.)
  - Item 5: Labour: A Magazine for All Workers, 1935; Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.2:no.5 (1935:Jan.)
  - Item 6: Labour: A Magazine for All Workers, 1935; Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.2:no.6 (1935:Feb.)
  - Item 7: Labour: A Magazine for All Workers, 1935; Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.2:no.7 (1935:Mar.)
  - Item 8: Labour: A Magazine for All Workers, 1935; Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.2:no.8 (1935:Apr.)
  - Item 9: Labour: A Magazine for All Workers, 1935; Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.2:no.9 (1935:May)
  - Item 10: Labour: A Magazine for All Workers, 1935; Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.2:no.10 (1935:June)
  - Item 11: Labour: A Magazine for All Workers, 1935; Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.2:no.11 (1935:July)
  - Item 12: Labour: A Magazine for All Workers, 1935; Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.2:no.12 (1935:Aug.)
  - Item 13: Labour: A Magazine for All Workers. Index, 1934-1935 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.2, September 1934 - August 1935
- The Labour Party. Labour: A Magazine for All Workers. Index, 1935-1937 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Labour: A Magazine for All Workers. Index, 1935-1936 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.3, September 1935 - August 1936
  - Item 2: Labour: A Magazine for All Workers. Index, 1936-1937 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.4, September 1936 - August 1937
- Labor Plays. Bibliographies, 1936-1945 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Annotated List of Labor Plays, 1945; Publication (Box 2, Folder 8)
    Author: Jean Carter Ogden; Nancy Faulkner
    Notes: Revised edition
  - Item 2: Annotated List of Labor Plays, 1945; Publication (Box 2, Folder 8)
    Notes: Revised edition, Copy 2
  - Item 3: Suggested Reading List: Novels, Plays, Biographies, Poetry Dealing with Social and Economic Problems, 1941; Publication (Box 2, Folder 8)
    Author: Elinor G. Black
  - Item 4: Affiliated Schools Scrapbook: Labor Drama, 1936; Publication (Box 2, Folder 8)
    Author: The Affiliated School for Workers
    Notes: v.1:no.1 (1936:Mar.)
  - Item 5: Annotated List of Labor Plays, 1938; Publication (Box 2, Folder 8)
    Author: Jean Carter
- Labor Plays. General, 1929-1939 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Finance Behind the Footlights:, 1930; Publication (Box 2, Folder 9)
    Author: Barbara Abel
  - Item 2: All For One: A Dramatic Skit, 1934; Publication (Box 2, Folder 9)
    Author: ILGWU (International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union)
  - Item 3: All For One: A Dramatic Skit, 1934; Publication (Box 2, Folder 9)
    Notes: Copy 2.
  - Item 4: All For One: A Dramatic Skit, 1934; Publication (Box 2, Folder 9)
    Notes: Copy 3.
  - Item 5: Bank Run: A Tragi-Comic Sketch in One Act., 1932; Publication (Box 2, Folder 9)
    Author: Hollace Ransdell
  - Item 6: Five Plays About Labor, 1939; Publication (Box 2, Folder 9)
    Author: Highlander Folk School
  - Item 7: The Great Philanthropist, Publication (Box 2, Folder 9)
    Author: Philip Barber
  - Item 8: Old Mr. Yaller Dog Take Him Away: A One Act Sketch Taken from Life in a Mill Village, 1929; Publication (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Item 9: The Shoe On The Other Foot, 1932; Publication (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Item 10: That's Inevitable: A Play in Three Episodes, 1930; Publication (Box 2, Folder 9)
    Author: Drama Interest Group
  - Item 11: That's Inevitable: A Play in Three Episodes, 1930; Publication (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Item 12: That's Inevitable: A Play in Three Episodes, 1930; Publication (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Item 13: A Wage Controversy (A Mock Trial), 1930; Publication (Box 2, Folder 9)
    Author: Denver Industrial Group
  - Item 14: We Ain't A-Goin' Back, Publication (Box 2, Folder 9)
    Author: Hazel Cunard
  - Item 15: Gimble Sprockets ("Something for Nothing"), Publication (Box 2, Folder 9)
    Author: Tom Thomas
    Notes: Reprinted from Workers Theatre.
- Labor Plays. Rural Plays, 1937; Publication (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Rural Plays: Part 1 for Advanced Amateurs. Dramas, Comedies, Tragedies, 1937; Publication (Box 2, Folder 10)
    Author: Nation Play Bureau, Federal Theatre Project
    Notes: Play Bureau Publication no. 15. Second edition
  - Item 2: Rural Plays: Part 2 Dramas, Comedies, Farces, 1937; Publication (Box 2, Folder 10)
    Notes: Play Bureau Publication no. 16.
  - Item 3: Rural Plays: Part 3, 1937; Publication (Box 2, Folder 10)
    Notes: Play Bureau Publication no. 17.
- Government Regulation of Trade Unions in Great Britain, Publication (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Government Regulation of Trade Unions in Great Britain: Part 2, Publication (Box 2, Folder 11)
    Author: V. Henry Rotheschild
    Notes: Confidential Draft
- Workers' Educational Association, 1924-1928 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: The Story of the Workers' Educational Association, 1903-1924, Publication (Box 2, Folder 12)
    Author: T. W. Price; R. H. Tawney
  - Item 2: The Workers' Educatinal Association. Its Methods and Organisations., Publication (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Item 3: Tenth Annual Report and Statement of Accounts, 1927-28, 1928; Publication (Box 2, Folder 12)
    Author: William Twaddle
  - Item 4: University Joint Committee Tutorial Classes, Publication (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Item 5: Co-Operators and Education, Publication (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Item 6: Southern District. Fourth Annual Report. 1927-1928, Publication (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Item 7: North Staffs District. Annual Report 1927-28, 1928; Publication (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Wissenschaft und Wirtschaft, Publication (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Wissenschaft und Wirtschaft, Publication (Box 2, Folder 13)
    Author: Hermann Schumacher
    Notes: Sonderdruck aus das Akademische Deutschland: Band 3
    Language: German.
- Miscellaneous German Documents, Publication (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Der Deutsche Schuhmachermeister, 1932; Publication (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Der Deutsche Schuhmachermeister, 1932; Publication (Box 2, Folder 15)
    Notes: v.6:nr.3 (1932:Jan.)
- Wege Zur Arbeit, 1932; Publication (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Wege Zur Arbeit, 1932; Publication (Box 2, Folder 16)
    Notes: v.1:heft 1 (1932:Apr. 22)
- Geschichte der Nationalokonomie, 1891; Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Geschichte der Nationalokonomie, 1891; Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
    Author: Diehl
    Notes: Handwritten lecture notes
- Politique Sociale et Ecomonie Politique, 1902; Publication (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Politique Sociale et Ecomonie Politique, 1902; Publication (Box 3, Folder 2)
    Author: Gustav Schmoller
    Language: French.
- Volkswirtschaftslehre, 1920; Publication (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Volkswirtschaftslehre, 1920; Publication (Box 3, Folder 3)
    Author: Carl Johannes Fuchs
    Notes: Sammlung Goschen, n.133. Second edition.
- Der Wahre Staat, 1921; Publication (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Der Wahre Staat, 1921; Publication (Box 3, Folder 4)
    Author: Othmar Spann
- Volkswirtschaftliche Gedankenstromungen Systeme und Theorien der Gegenwart besonders in Deutschland, 1925; Publication (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Volkswirtschaftliche Gedankenstromungen Systeme und Theorien der Gegenwart besonders in Deutschland, 1925; Publication (Box 3, Folder 5)
    Author: Hans Honegger
    Notes: Braun's Kleine Handbucher
- Das Deutsche Volkseinkommen, 1926; Publication (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Das Deutsche Volkseinkommen, 1926; Publication (Box 3, Folder 6)
    Author: Erich Rogowski
    Notes: Volkswirtschaftliche Studien, heft 13.
- Archiv fur Sozialwissenschaft und Sozialpolitik, 1927; Publication (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Archiv fur Sozialwissenschaft und Sozialpolitik, 1927; Publication (Box 3, Folder 7)
    Author: K. A. Wittfogel; Arthur Salz; Stephan Bauer; Robert Michels; Karl Mannheim; Franz Oppenheimer; S. P. Altmann
    Notes: Bd.57:heft 2
- Geschichte der Politischen Parteien in Deutschland, 1928; Publication (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Geschichte der Politischen Parteien in Deutschland, 1928; Publication (Box 3, Folder 8)
    Author: L. Bergstrasser
    Notes: Schriftenreihe der Verwaltungsakademie Berlin, Band 4.
- Wirtschaftsdemokratie, 1928; Publication (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Wirtschaftsdemokratie Ihr Wesen, Weg und Ziel, 1928; Publication (Box 3, Folder 9)
    Author: Fritz Naphtali
- Die Wertschassende Arbeitslosenfursorge, 1928; Publication (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Die Wertschassende Arbeitslosenfursorge, 1928; Publication (Box 3, Folder 10)
    Author: K. Wilhelmi
    Notes: Bucherei des Arbeitsrechts, Neue Folge. Band 8.
- Deutsche Sozialpolitif, 1918-1928, 1929; Publication (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Deutsche Sozialpolitif, 1918-1928, 1929; Publication (Box 3, Folder 11)
- International Review for the Social Activities of the Churches, 1929; Publication (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: International Review for the Social Activities of the Churches, 1929; Publication (Box 3, Folder 12)
    Author: Adolf Keller
    Notes: Sonderdruck aus Stockholm. Cover in English, German, and French
- Die Verhandlungen der Sachverstandigenkommission fur Fragen der Arbeitslosenversicherung, 1929; Publication (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Die Verhandlungen der Sachverstandigenkommission fur Fragen der Arbeitslosenversicherung, 1929; Publication (Box 3, Folder 13)
    Notes: Sonderveroffentrlichung der Reichsarbeitsblattes
- Die Wohnengsnot und das Wohnungselend in Deutschland, 1929; Publication (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Die Wohnengsnot und das Wohnungselend in Deutschland, 1929; Publication (Box 3, Folder 14)
    Author: Bruno Schwan
    Notes: Schriften heft 7
- Die Kriegsschulden, 1930; Publication (Box 3, Folder 15)